

### Profile

Excellent with computers and technology. Experienced and skillful Senior Customer Service Agent providing high quality service to customers, while addressing and meeting all needs. Track record of serving as an effective liaison between companies and customers

# Employment History

## Senior Customer Support Specialist at Sciplay, Austin

March 2019 — Present

- Provided personalized customer support that went above and beyond the customer's expectations, resulting in a increase in customer loyalty and retention.
- Developed and implemented customer support procedures such as macros that improved customer service and reduced customer wait times
- Worked Closely with our QA Team, to address customer concerns on current issues, and reported this in Jira and to the correct teams.

### Customer Support Specialist at 2k Entertainment, Austin

November 2018 — March 2019

- Analyzed customer service data to identify areas of improvement, resulting in a reduction in customer service issues
- Built a Macro Database to quickly address common concerns or issues.

#### **Customer Support at Blizzard Entertainment, Austin**

October 2017 — October 2018

- Maintained the Highest CSAT Score among 200+ Agents for the duration of my Contract, while holding one of the highest Tickets Per hour.
- Developed and maintained customer service policies and procedures to ensure customer complaints are handled consistently and efficiently

### Education

Computer Science, San Antonio College, San Antonio

Coding, UTSA BootCamp, San Antonio

August 2023 — February 2024

## **◄** References

Bijan Olfati from Swords of Northshire 210-850-3803

#### **Details**

Austin
United States
5628462968
codylthomp@gmail.com

#### Links

LinkedIn

#### **Skills**

**Multitasking Skills** 

**Problem Solving Skills** 

Strong Communication Skills

Highly organized and efficient

**Customer Satisfaction** 

**Quality Assurance** 

**Customer Issue Resolution** 

**Macro Creation** 

Technical Support